This is so nice.
Look how nice this view is.
Alright guys, so we made it down to the beach.
We're gonna go boogie boarding right now.
Two miles into our hike.
We made it to the top of the mountain.
Look how beautiful the sunset is.
Alright guys, welcome back to the vlog.
This is my Costa Rica vlog where I'm actually going to Costa Rica.
And you'll see that in the clips later on.
But I'm playing 18 right now with like a Big John.
That's Striped It.
Pretty pure.
Oh, Kyle Striped It.
Striped It, old heart.
Oh, a lot of heart over that golf ball.
And I woke up at like 6.40ish this morning.
Played early morning 18.
Yeah.
But.
Kyle dragging me out of bed this morning, 5.30 in the morning.
Yeah, at least it's not Saturday.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
If it was Sunday, I probably would have faded respectfully.
Respectfully.
But it's good to get out here.
No, for sure.
So we're going to go and play Quick Dad.
Quick Dad.
Another nine.
Yep.
I like that you film on the iPhone too.
Isn't that funny?
It actually has a good camera.
It does.
I know you could, but I don't know.
When we did the run together, I walked in.
Kai had the whole production team.
Running.
Did we just start running?
Is that what we're going to do?
There we go.
Oh my god.
Ty, we go slow.
Big J Run Club, we're gonna go real slow this afternoon, alright?
Yeah, that was a lot.
That was a good day.
Yeah,
it's a great golf shot.
All right, call for more.
A little par 5 in you.
You got to get some...
All right, we're going to strike this down.
We're in the fairway.
We have two holes left.
Honestly, I haven't been playing bad.
My wrist is a little sore.
I spent a total of seven hours grinding yesterday, working my game.
Five hours on the course, two hours putting.
Not great.
It's a big day for you.
Big day for me, but that's what you gotta do if you want to be
good.
You're going to be great if you do that.
I'll be great.
so good
all right let's eat a little buttery cut all right let's see this rocket hit
it oh it looks so cool in black dot
see it like with the stick it does you can like see it like
All
right guys, so made part of that hole.
Yeah, we're on the last hole on 18.
And then I got the workout.
Then I got a putter fitting later today with TaylorMade.
But yeah, long day.
Enjoying my day.
And yeah, I'm alone.
Oh
no.
Whoa, why did that happen?
Do you want me to give a little zoom action or no?
Is that crazy?
Yeah, we don't, let's not, let's not rely on John on the zoom.
John, just point and shoot, guy.
Yeah, come on.
An ace on camera.
Oh, two peas.
All hard.
Just a quick push cut.
Just gone.
There you go.
Spin.
That wasn't as cool.
You like AI that and make it like spin back for me?
Except just put it in the hole.
Yeah, seriously.
Yeah, it's a big one.
You'll make that.
Oh, all heart in
the rain too.
Yeah.
Wave to the gallery.
It's just us.
It's just.
We might be the only.
We're done with Alex.
Almost our master.
We've been on there for 15 minutes.
Level 11.
And we're going to go home and shower.
And then see Emma.
And see you guys in the next clip.
Alright guys, Emma is here.
Hi guys.
Emma made me a painting for my apartment.
It's really bad.
No, I'm sure it looks good.
It turned out terribly I told her to give me a craft to make and
she said paint a mountain I don't paint.
Okay guys, i'm here with kai now and i'm gonna show her the painting and
hope that she likes it Okay There it is Do you like it?
Wow, that's sick kai.
It's don't lie.
It's terrible.
You're lying That one's me because it's during the pizza I was thinking Is it
that one or that one could be you This one's in a bikini
Wait what happened with this one I didn't want to give him a helmet He
was just like YOLO No this is sick how did you get this like hard
Wait you actually like it No I really like it I'm in shock This is
spackle When you get a hole in the wall but you use to fill it
It's spackle This is sick.
You know what my mom's doing?
My mom's doing this school too.
Really?
I want to do it now.
This is super cool.
I really like it.
Yeah, I really like it.
Where do you think it's from?
I thought it was so terrible.
Wait, can you put it up when you move?
Yeah.
It should be like the first piece of art.
Yeah, I'm not going to move.
Oh, I'm so happy that you liked it.
Thank you so much for coming over and making me a painting.
Thank you so much.
This is sick.
I can't believe you liked it.
I signed it in the corner too.
No, on the front.
I gave a sign, a wanky face, and a heart.
Wow, thank you.
Yes.
I love it.
Yes, of course.
I'm so happy that you like it, friend.
All right, guys, so we got the bathing suit on.
And now we're going to head to the beach.
Everyone is still getting ready.
But like, getting really gained right now.
But yeah, so we're going to go to the beach.
and then figure out what we just did.
All right, guys, we're only moving right now.
We'll walk into the beach club.
We got beach day passes today.
The weather's really good.
All right, everyone's just out.
Hey, how are you?
I'm good.
How are you?
So me and Marley right now are just sitting down.
Everyone's in the pool, but yeah, we're just...
No, I'm like smiling, so now I look better.
So we're just waiting.
Everyone's in the pool, but yeah, we're just chilling right here.
It's really nice.
The weather's nice today, so exciting.
I'm going to go on my GoPro.
I'm going to be a beast.
The water's terrible.
There's so many rocks.
Really?
Yeah, you can't even swim.
We tried, but couldn't.
Okay, so maybe we're not going to do that.
Only this or this too?
No, only this.
Thank you.
Look they all came.
I'm wondering where they are.
They all went to get ice creams.
How's your guys' ice cream?
I just ate down my whole peanut butter ice cream.
It was good.
It was good?
Want some, Paul?
Oh wait, we can walk to the beach from here?
Got some comida, right?
Got some comida right now.
Alright.
Alright guys, so we made it down to the beach.
We're gonna go boogie boarding right now.
And I did not bring my SD card for my GoPro, so that kinda sucks,
but we'll keep you posted.
Alright vlog, so this is my dinner fit.
Um.
That's what we're working with.
It's dressed for Alison and Olivia, I'm like obsessed with it.
But it's my dinner fit.
Could I steal these?
No you can take them.
Let me show them the full fit.
So we really went for like diva, like we're in Greece, even though we're in
Costa Rica.
We went for like, I'm in Greece, like this is the vibe, so.
I'm in Greece, this is the vibe, these are my sunglasses.
This is a dress and I'm wearing these little cute heels I bought.
And yeah, that's the fit, so hope you guys enjoy.
Marley, where's my sunglasses?
This is looking hard walking in heels, not gonna lie.
This zone?
That's okay.
Powering through.
We are walking right now.
So nothing.
It's a banger.
It's so pretty, yo.
Oh my god, look how nice this is.
This is so nice.
Guys, we're gonna get some good photos.
What?
We're gonna get some good photos.
Yes!
This is so nice.
Guys, look how beautiful the sunset is.
Listen to the gong.
It's amazing.
amazing.
Almost as beautiful as you.
Is that Rizchat?
Yeah this is like so nice.
It's so hot guys.
I absolutely never want to leave Costa Rica.
I just wanna move here.
It's amazing.
It is beautiful here.
Alright vlog so we just had some food and it's like late now but we
had some food and I think we're gonna go back to the room now and
play some card games Cause why not?
Oh you guys are excited?
Oh we're so excited!
Oh no!
So cute!
What's the plan with the whole strip?
Can I show them something?
No, no, no No I'm not, what do you show them?
Oh wow Alright and now So we're gonna go back to the room now and
yeah See you guys soon Okay guys, so we're on our hike right now
with Sexy Schwab.
And this is a long hike so stay tuned.
All right guys, we made it to the top of the mountain.
This is so nice.
So nice.
We're like two miles into our hike.
Yeah, it's great.
I really hope this is.
It's great.
That's the views in St.
Louis.
this is the house oh i'm just so warm it's great that's the views insane
i'm a big dog emma i am big dog i haven't complained at all trust
me i want to wait let me cut in front of you so you can't
i want to cut far so that nobody can complain about my illusion okay actually
we're all going These crabs, there's so many crabs
here.
It's insane.
Look at this big.
Massive claws.
Insane views on this hike.
I don't think you're sweating a lot, but it's all right.
It's all right.
Sit down and hide.
Look
how nice this view is.
This view is actually insane.
I'm flying tomorrow to New York.
But there's a slight issue.
I didn't book my hotel room.
So I'm trying to figure out right now.
Because I have to be there for three days and the worst day so we're
figuring out right now in your city but yeah, this is quite the
You know poop show I guess but we're figuring out and solve it.
Yeah, I mean we can't be serious Doesn't get much better than that
All you guys on this
Back with my best friend Emma
Best friends for life.